creativefabrica.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy of www.creativefabrica.com

Website Privacy Policy  
This privacy statement applies to users of the Website, www.taxamo.com (the “site”) and any of its subdomains. We at Taxamo are committed to protecting your privacy and this privacy statement sets out the use we make of any information that we may obtain by the use of our site.

The site is operated by Taxamo, 1 Library Place, Killorglin, Co. Kerry, Ireland (referred to here as “we”/“us”/“our”).

This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Taxamo when you access our website, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information.

Using the site  
By using our site, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current privacy policy as posted on this site.

Collection of information  
Personal information  
This refers to any information you submit to us and that identifies you personally. This includes contact information supplied by you within online forms, such as your name, email address, company name, address, phone number and any other information about yourself or your company. It may also include any information about you that is available publicly on the Internet from platforms such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and Google, or any publicly available information from service providers that we may use.

Navigational information: “cookies”  
Taxamo uses cookies and similar technologies on our website. You can find more information about our Cookie Policy here. By using our website, you agree to Taxamo’s use of cookies. You can opt out at any time by using the specific opt-outs listed in our Cookie Policy.

Please note that when you purchase any of the Taxamo products and services, we collect your data in relation to the details set out in your contract of sale found in your terms and conditions.

Use of information collected  
When you voluntarily provide personal data to us in order for us to contact you or to provide notifications to you, Taxamo’s legal basis for processing your personal data is by consent. We will only use your data in accordance with the reason given at the time you provide consent. This includes:

Improving your browsing experience by personalising your website experience  
Updating you with information which we think may be of interest to you by either post, email or online advertising  
Responding to a request for information you may have made  
Following up on a support query you have made through our website  
We may use a combination of personal and navigational information to help us understand our target market and improve our marketing and messaging efforts. Taxamo will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others.

Opting out of communications  
To opt out of communications and update personal communication preference please email Taxamo at the following email address: marketing@taxamo.com

Where we store your personal information  
When you submit a request via any of the taxamo.com “contact us” forms we store the personal data that you provide to us (your contact details) in either our CRM system (HubSpot) or our support system (Help Scout).

The personal information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by third party suppliers operating outside the EEA that comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Disclosure  
Taxamo will disclose your information where required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (i) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (ii) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (iii) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Taxamo, our users or others. You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

Notification of changes  
If we change this Privacy Policy we will post the amended Policy on our website so that you are always aware of how we collect, use, and disclose your personal information.

Latest revision: May 2018
